topnudegalleries.com 2017-05-08

# Privacy Policy | Top Nude Galleries

The Topnudegalleries.com is posting this privacy statement to inform our customers of our policies with regards to privacy. The information provided here gives our policy regarding gathering and dissemination of information for our website.

Any personal information (email address, home address, etc.) which we obtain from visitors/customers will not be sold or shared with any third party. All information gathered is used for internal purposes only. You may exercise the right to not receive future mailings, and information on removing yourself from our e-mail lists is given below.

In some situations, we may be legally obligated to disclose information about you to the government or other third parties. If asked or required by law, we may release information about you to law enforcement, government or officers of the court if we believe it is necessary or appropriate to investigate or resolve potential problems or inquiries.

The Topnudegalleries.com gathers information about its visitors in the following ways:

  * Site statistics, including, but not limited to, the capture of IP addresses, browser type, operating system used, and Internet cookies, that provide both aggregated non-personally identifiable information, as well as information that may allow us to identify you personally.
  * Contest and Registration forms.
  * Newsletters and mailing lists.
  * Orders placed for products and services via www.Topnudegalleries.com.

We capture your IP address when you enter our ordering system to assist with the diagnosis of problems with our server and to traceback fraudulent credit card usage. Your IP address is used to help match you and your shopping cart.

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart so that you can go in and out of the ordering system without losing your order.

Browser type and operating system type data is collected as part of our analytics processes. We may also use the services of reputable third parties to provide us with data collection, reporting, ad response measurement, and site analytics in a non-personally identifiable manner.

Contest and Registration forms on our site require users to give us contact information including addresses and email addresses. Customer contact information from the registration forms may be used to send information about our company and its products. This information is also used to contact you if necessary.

Mailing list communications from The Topnudegalleries.com are sent only to those requesting an opt-in subscription and are used to notify readers of site updates, promotions, and other business communications. You may exercise the right to not receive future mailings, and information on removing yourself from our e-mail lists is given below.

On-line ordering is available on our website for customers to purchase products and services. We collect contact information and financial payment information, including credit card numbers. This information is used to send product and services orders, and this information may also be used to send other information to you regarding our products and services. We may also use the contact information to get in touch with you if necessary. Financial payment information that is collected is used to verify account ownership and bill you for products and services purchased. You may remove yourself from our mailing list and/or e-mailing list at any time; information on removing yourself is given below.

You may choose to add interactivity to our content through the use of third-party social networking sites, such as Facebook or Twitter, or through other third-party plug-ins and applications. When doing so, access may be provided in both directions from and to your personal social media profile. It is also possible that non-personally identifiable information can be provided from your interaction with our content. By utilizing our site in coordination with such third-party social networking sites, plug-ins, or applications, you consent to the use of such information by us in accordance with our privacy policy. In addition, Topnudegalleries.com cannot control how such information is used by these third parties, plug-ins, and applications, and it is possible that that information may be publically viewed by other users of these social networking sites, plug-ins, and applications.

Social networking sites, plug-ins, and applications generally have their own privacy settings where you can control what data is shared. We recommend you consult their privacy policies and terms of use.

The information we collect in connection with our online forums is used to provide an interactive experience with the forum members. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, or services.
